Thank you for watching.
And now, it's time for our host, Banana Hong, to welcome you to Nogizaka Construction Workshops.
Oh, no.
I'm not here.
And now, after all this time, the Nogizaka girls have been forced to reschedule their performances at the center of the city.
Please announce today's program!
Halloween Party 2024!
Aaaaaaah!
Today is the last day of October and we are going to have a Halloween party where we will ask our members to dress up in costumes and enjoy playing games in teams!
This time, we will take a survey from the members, and we will make a request for someone to dress up in a costume of his/her choice.
Let's have the members appear on stage.
Nurse... is it a waste?
I'm going to inject you with something... nostalgic.
Next one, please.
This one... this one... this one's good, isn't it?
It's a classic.
I love it.
Pause.
I thought I was going to arrest you.
I hope we don't have to pause.
That's nice. That's cute.
Let's move on to the next one.
Go ahead.
Shibata?
Let me be your goddess of victory, I'm begging you... this is a "kodaikko"... do this forever, I can't do it forever...
I can do it forever.
This is a modern nurse.
You look good.
It looks good on you. It looks good on you.
Stop the pain, stop the pain.
I like it.
I love it.
Next, please.
I see... a pirate.
A pirate... it suits you...
Come on, love, let's go hunting!
I'm going to the needle... and he's going to the needle... what? It's nice to be told like that from a dream, isn't it?
I'm in love... but not with the staff...
Oh, wow!
Is that Sakaguchi?
Let's play with boredom.
Let's play.
He's a bad boy!
Yay!
He's cute, isn't he?
Yay, yay, yay!
Hey, it's Sakaguchi!
I didn't recognize you for a second.
Yes, yes, that's good.
Let's keep going!
Here we go!
Thank you for watching!
Oh, my God, what is this?
Is this a cosplay?
What is this?
What's with the apron?
What is this, like a fire? What is this, like a fire?
What is it?
Side dish.
Come in... we put a lot of love into it.
What's this?
The deli guy.
The deli!
It's a humble "Hello Inn", isn't it?
Is this what you have, Governor?
I see...
Here we go!
Here it comes!
What is this?
A station? No, it's not.
Cab or bus?
Bus driver.
Mr. Himura, you may not have enough money left.
Wait a minute.
What is it? Electronic money or something?
It's about the lack of electronic money and someone else.
Why do you keep mentioning Himura-san by name?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
That's fine. I'm happy for you.
I'll keep going.
Here we go.
It's a classic.
Oh, this is it.
It's like Halloween, isn't it?
Like this, like this.Like this. Like this.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'll buy you candy!
It's the best way to celebrate Halloween, isn't it?
Here we go.
It looks good on you.
Little Red Riding Hood. It's Little Red Riding Hood.
Don't eat the wolf.
I love it.
It's a little red hood.
It's adorable.
Let's get on with it.
This one's good, too.
What's this?
A black cat.
I see a fish!
It's a cat.
It's silly.
It's cute.
And here we go.
I did it!
This is a black cat, and this is a white cat.
White's good, too.
White's nice, too.
Black is good, too.
Will you pick me up?
It's an abandoned cat.
I didn't know that.
This one's worth raising.This is worth raising.
Catism
Here we go... and here we go... and here we go.
I like this one.
A witch, but a student kind of witch.
That's right.
I'm gonna make you so soft and juicy.
That's some scary magic.
It's like boiling you in a cauldron.
That's the kind of magic
I'm gonna make you so soft and juicy
Scary, isn't it?
Let's move on... to the next one.
This is a character from a comic book.
That's awesome!
Yuuki, go with Eagle and look for Nyaago.
This is the power of the Chainsaw Man.
Here we go.
This one...
It's cute, but...
Yes, yes, yes...
He's riding a dinosaur.
So cute!
I know, right?
You don't like women who ride dinosaurs?
What did you say?
Don't you like women who ride dinosaurs?
I don't know what you're talking about.
This happens all the time.
It's cute, too. They're cute, too.
They're cute, aren't they?
Yeah.
It's nice.
It's good.
Okay, okay.
Okay, we're down to the last one.
Let's go this way.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes yes
I wonder what he'll say...
I wonder what he's going to say?
It's good... it's here at last... kamakiri...
It's Halloween... so we had everyone dress up in costumes... but this time...
This is the one requested by the other members.
Is that how it is?
Yoda's old nurse. I wonder who said that.
Yes, sir.
Why did you want her to dress like this?
I thought Yoda had a cute little animal-like quality.
I thought if I became a nurse, I'd rush in even if the patient wasn't sick.
I decided on this one.
I see. Because it's cute.
And Iwamoto's. This is a classic.
I knew this one was good
I wonder who said this.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Iwamoto!
Why?
Mr. Iwamoto... at live shows, he always says, "You guys!Mr. Iwamoto, at his live performances, you always say things like, "Hey, you guys!
I'd like to be abused by someone of the same sex.
I see.
It's a bit strong.
Yes, she is.
She's cute, but...
She has beautiful feet.
Yes, they are.
I'm embarrassed.
Embarrassing.
This is a good time.
It's a good time.
Good times.
Yes, I've got a hangnail.
So, nurse.
Yes, sir.
This is the bus driver.
Bus driver.
That's cool.
Who said this?
Oh yeah who
So you're a dinosaur and slightly hard-bay.
Yes, sir.
The bus driver sounded so calm.
In a very calm voice.
"We'll stop next time.
I'm like, "Oh, we're stopping? I'd be like, "Oh, we're stopping?
But first of all, I thought, "Iyoki, you do narration for a living.
I thought it would be a good fit. I thought it would look amazing on you.
Oh, so that's how it is.
But when I first heard that Iyoki was a bus driver.
I was like, "Uh-oh.
That's for sure.
A bus driver on Halloween.
He's an endo type.
This is a real occupational pattern here.
There's that kind of thing.
Well, it's the devil's standard, isn't it?
That's so cute.
Who said that?
I did.
Potstickers.
I'd like to see it on a potato long.
I'd like to see you in a potato long.
I'm more interested in the potstickers.
I made a mistake.
I'll take the first one.
This is Red Riding Hood.
She's cute.
This kind of thing suits you, too.
I wonder who said this.
Yes, sir.
Cool Little Red Riding Hood.
Why?
Ever since I first saw Miku.
I couldn't help but want her to dress up as this Red Riding Hood.I couldn't resist dressing her up as this Red Riding Hood.
Heh.
And the black cat is so cute!
I love black cats.
So cute!
It's a hikikoman.
He's a hikikoman.
Who told you this?
I did.
Why is this a black cat?
I had an image of Kakki as a strong man...
I had an image of Kakki as a solid person... or an older sister...
I wanted to see how cute he is.
I wanted to see a cute Kakki.
So I asked him to make a request for me.
You're right, it's not white.
It's black.
Heh.
Black, you're a little picky about Kamaki.
Kamaki.
You dropped your pumpkin, pumpkin.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, driver.
And on the other side, a white cat.
White.
White cat.
White's not fair anymore.
It's true, isn't it?
Who said that?
Yes, I did.Yes, sir.
Oh, you have a background.
Why?
I was thinking of what to dress Mayu-chan in.
All I could think of was a cat.
Oh...
She's pale, so a white cat would definitely suit her.
I feel like you've already established yourself as a character.
Including her voice.
Oh, really?
That's scary.
Oh my God, that's great!
And last but not least, here's the best part!
Dinosaur!
What's that called, a girl riding a dinosaur?
A cowboy riding a dinosaur?
Cowboy!
To be honest, when I heard this was a Halloween project...
I thought I'd wear something cute for Halloween today
I thought I'd put on something cute for Halloween and make a little heart in my eyes.
And now look at this...
I really wanted something different.
I really...
I wanted something cute.
The white cat.
A white cat?
No, it doesn't look like a white cat.
A black cat then.
No, it doesn't look like a cat.
A dinosaur, then.Dinosaurs, then.
Dinosaurs are fast, fast, fast.
And the promu... kamakiri.
Well, if we don't do the Kamakiri here...
That's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying... it's the real thing.
And after that, a powerful battle with bullets!
Don't miss the hot cosplay game tournament!
From here on, we split into two teams, ghosts and pumpkins, and played Halloween games!
The winning team gets a tasty Herbie, and the losing team gets...
And the losing team will get a serious badge.
So you'd better go for it. Let's play the first game, Mr. Ice Village.
The first game is Halloween Basket!
The first game is a fruit basket with the players dressed up in Halloween costumes.
The member who couldn't sit down will be the devil, and the team that could sit all the members down will get 1 point each time.
The first team to choose a theme is the pea team by lottery.
When I read out the name of the game and said "Good start," Pea had to sit down right away, too.
I'll take that empty spot, okay?
Pea, you don't understand, do you?
Pull, Pea.
Okay, let's draw.
Let's see who's got the black stand.
Akashi police, please.
Akashi Police.
That was great. I thought Endo wouldn't sit down at all.
There's Hamura.
Hamura was amazing. The cat hit Little Red Riding Hood.
I see.
Interesting. Interesting.
This is...
I'll have to watch this one to make sure I get it right.
Yes, these all moved most of the time, but...
I didn't know there was such a thing as an only child.
Oh, just the black one?
I see. They didn't move.
I'm glad I didn't move.
And you all have siblings?
Hamura... we bumped into each other at the end.
We're on the same team.
It's so hard to sit in the same place.
I see.
Sorry.
That's why he was last.
Endo, you're so soft.
I shouldn't have sat here.
Why didn't you sit here when it was empty?
I thought you were taking a spot from the enemy team.
I didn't say that.
Just sit wherever is available.
You can sit anywhere but where you're sitting.
Pumpkin team has one point.
Okay, Ichiro, you're up.
Draw lots and read them out.
Here you go.
Anyone who's ever won a gold medal at least once in school.
Okay, let's start.
Wow! Wow.
Givi givi.
Oh, wow.
Whoa!
Shibata.
Wow, there's only two of you... have you both won gold medals at a club?
The only thing I'm proud of is winning a gold medal at a club meeting.
Wow!
When did you win?
All my life... kindergarten, elementary school, junior high...
That's amazing.
I've never missed a class twice.
That's great.
That's wonderful.
You're in good health.
Yeah, that's great.
And Kawasaki?
Yes, they won the gold medal at the high school competition.
Really?
That's great.
You've been there?
Yes, sir.
It's a long way to go.
It was a little dangerous.
Isn't it a little late for akazuki?
It's just there and then there, but it's too late.
I had dried plums on me.
We could've gone there.
When I first read it, I thought you might have taken it.When I first read it, I thought you'd be taking Mr. Umezawa or something.
Oh, I see.
Sure.
I thought he'd move, but he was going to sit there.
I was going to go this way.
You're taking a break?
I have my moments.
I see.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Did you miss elementary school, middle school and high school?
Basically, I never missed a day, but I didn't win any gold medals.
I thought I'd have won the gold medal, so they were after me.
And you're two years younger than me.
Well, I'm minus one for the pumpkin team, and I got a point for the ghost team, so I'm 1-1.
One-one-one.
Let's go, Jesse Butter.
Okay, here we go.
Who has a photo of a member's sleeping face?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I knew it was a curse.
It's Endo.
It's really cursed.
This thing doesn't work? Ozaki doesn't have it?
I don't like having my face taken.
I can't do it to others.
I mean, I can't do it.
But I'm sure you've had your face taken a lot.
I don't sleep with many people.
Really?Really?
You won the gold medal for Favorite Society.
That's really strong.
And everyone else has one?
Well, even the members. I've got one of Mr. Himuro's.
You have one of mine, too.
Do you take their lunches too?
I don't take lunch boxes, but I happened to be next to him.
I just happened to be next to him.
They were sleeping.
Who's holding it?
Seiya or Rei-chan?
I see.
Who has it, Ume or someone else?
I think I have most of the third-termers.
Wow.
They're all tired, so they sleep a lot.
They're just saving that kind of thing.
They look so cute and vulnerable.
I see.
You'll take the pincers, too?
I will.
Whose?
I took some of Yoda's.
He looks like he's sleeping.
To be honest, I think I'm on the receiving end.
I see.
I wonder who has the best sleeping face.
Ayamen. Ayamayo.
What?
I sleep pretty well.
She sleeps a lot.
But Ikeda and the others were filmed at the tree.
I don't like having my sleeping face photographed.
So I tried not to take pictures of everyone.
But then I ended up on the receiving end.
I guess I should take pictures back.
I'm taking pictures back.
I have to sit down soon.
Go for it.
I'll do my best.
I'm not good at singing
Here we go!
Who's not good at singing
Oops!
This is already efficiently off and on and off
Yes, it is.
I'm not good at singing, but I don't like to move.
That's a lot of moving.
I'm not very good at singing.
He never went to karaoke in middle school or high school.
That's because he was a skater.
That's why I didn't go to karaoke until I joined Nogizaka.
So...
I'm really bad at it.
I see.
And Chie Ichino? Chie Ichino, too.
I'm not good at it either, and I really don't sing karaoke with my friends.
How can you be an idol?
You have to sing.
I really hate it, but I enjoy it.
Singing at live shows is fun, right?
It's fun when I'm with the other members.
But if I have to sing my own part, it's not good.
I can't do it anymore.
Oh, no...
What about Kuromi?
Well, recently I've been getting a lot of compliments on my voice, but I'm not sure if I'm that good or if I can do it with confidence.
But if you ask me if I'm that good or if I can do it with confidence, I'm still not so good.
Kuromi, you can't turn your head this way?
That must be tough.
Tamura, too?
Yes, I do.
I like singing.
But I'm not good at it.
I like singing, but I'm not very good at it.
But with so many people in the group, there are people who are good at it, so I guess compared to them or something.
One point again to the Haunted Team for being Kawasaki.
The ghost team is very strong.
Let's get started.
All right, all right, all right.
It's empty, it's empty, it's empty, it's empty.
Sometimes I get blanked out all of a sudden.
Like when the waterworks come on in a jar.
Team number three is on the line, sir.
That's what I'm talking about.Thanks to you!
Nozaka46 34th single to be released
Selection members will be announced in the next program
The selected members for the 34th single will be
also issued during the Don Rampage
I'm Yuki Judas. This is Semi-array.
Please subscribe to our channel.
...... quas